Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Unidentified Programs, Films, etc., Series 6.
  - K's, Subseries 11.
    - King's Shadow (logs 384-404) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 November 21; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 16)
      On container, "CTN/11-21-77/R21/Logs384-404/H50-"King's Shadow"."
    - King's Shadow (logs 405-414) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 November 21; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 17)
      On container, "CTN/11-21-77/R22/Logs405-414/H50-"Tread King's Shadow"."
    - Killer of the Year (logs 1525-1554) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 April 21; open reel audio tape (Box 1104, Folder 11)
      On container, "CTN/4-21-77/R79/LOGS 1525-1554/AT-"Killer Of Year"."
    - Killer of the Year (logs 1555-1558) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 April 21; open reel audio tape (Box 1104, Folder 12)
      On container, "CTN/4-21-77/R80/LOGS 1555-1558/AT-"Killer Of Year"."
    - Killer of the Year -- Sound Recordings, 1977 April 25; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1133, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS-Studio Center/"Killer Of The Year"/4-25-77."
  - L's, Subseries 12.
    - Looking Good [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1979 May 9; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 969, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS TV Center/Looking Good/Artist HEA/CBS/406/15 ips/Level 406 +3/Dolby A/24 TRK/5-9-79/Reel 1 of 1/Catalogue No. 3794."
    - A Long Time Ago (Logs 575-607) -- Sound Recordings, 1978 November 20; open reel audio tape (Box 1105, Folder 1)
      On container, "CED/11-20-78/R24/LOGS 575-607/H50 "A Long Time Ago"."
    - Le Mans -- Sound Recordings, 1971 June 3; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1146, Folder 8)
      On container, "CBS Studio Center/Acct. No. 15254/"Le Mans" Demo Record/John Neal & Jim Corbett."
    - Le Mans -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1146, Folder 9)
      On container, "Le Mans/First Chorus Of First Tune/985-2248."
  - M's, Subseries 13.
    - Merry-Go-Round --Sound Recordings, 1968 July 11; open reel audio tape (Box 1100, Folder 2)
      On container, ""Merry-Go-Round Barrel Organ" MR2B."
    - Man on Moon (Logs 294-325) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 October 19; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 12)
      On container, "CTN/10-19-77/R17/Logs294-325/H50-"Man on Moon"."
    - Man on Moon (Logs 326-337) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 October 19; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 13)
      On container, "CTN/10-19-77/R18/Logs326-337/H50-"Man on Moon""EastWind"."
    - Mobile Maidens (logs 1267-1301) -- Sound Recordigns, 1977 September 15; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 8)
      On container, "CTN/9-15-77/R54/LOGS 1267-1301/Mobile Maidens."
    - Mobile Maidens (logs 1302-1314) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 September 15; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 9)
      On container, "CTN/9-15-77/R55/LOGS 1302-1314/Mobile Maidens."
    - Member of the Family [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1977 December 7; open reel audio tape (Box 1107, Folder 12)
      On container, "CTN/12-7-77/Mixi-Take 4/"Member Of The Family/50th Anniversary."
    - Merry-Go-Round -- Sound Recordings, 1968 July 11; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1153, Folder 9)
      On container, "Merry-Go-Round (Barrel Organ) MR2A/1. Dolores Waltz "The Fabulous Arab"/2. The Faithful Hussar (Frantzen)/3. La Paloma (Yradier)."
    - The Monkey Opera, 1982 April 17 (Box 1852)
      Jave DeLynn, librettist.
  - N's, Subseries 14.
    - Ninth Step (logs 252-268) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 September 30; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 9)
      On container, "CTN/9-30-77/R14/Logs252-268/H50-"Ninth Step"."
    - Ninth Step (logs 269-292) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 September 30; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 10)
      On container, "CTN/9-30-77/R15/Logs269-292/H50-"Ninth Step"."
    - Ninth Step (log 293) -- Sound Recordings, 1977 September 30; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 11)
      On container, "CTN/9-30-77/R16/Logs293/H50-"Ninth Step"."
  - O's, Subseries 15.
    - Open Windows -- Scores, Orchestral scores (Box 18)
      Orchestral scores by Franz Waxman for an unidentified production titled "Open Windows"
    - Outside Man [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1977 January 25; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1076, Folder 11)
      On container, "R2/Outside Man/1-25-77."
    - Outside Man [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1977 January 25; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1136, Folder 20)
      On container, "R1/Outside Man/1-25-77/Production No. 5996-4647."
    - The O'Connors -- Papers, 1988 November 29; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 16)
      Post production schedule no. 2.
  - P's, Subseries 16.
    - Penelope Beware (logs 3564-3636) -- Sound Recordings, 1966 January 19; open reel audio tape (Box 1003, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/1-19-66/Reel/Log 3564-3636 (INC 3555-3636)/Print Takes Remix/#0000-9612 Penelope Beware (Pilot)."
    - Prophecy -- Sound Recordings, 1963 August 22; open reel audio tape (Box 1100, Folder 18)
      On container, "RH "Prophecy" P.Sawtelle."
    - Prophecy -- Sound Recordings, 1963 August 22; open reel audio tape (Box 1100, Folder 19)
    - Punk and Disorderly -- Open Reel Tapes and Documents, 1980 [?] (Box 1821, Folder unknown container)
    - Jackson Pollock: A Portrait -- Sound Recordings, 1984; 1 sound cassette (Box 1852)
      Tape contains: 1. Closing Montage -- 2. Western Theme -- 3. Mexican Theme -- 4. Energy -- 5. Indian Theme -- 6. Non-Objective -- 7. Home Movies -- 8. Bad City -- 9. "Hot Diggety" (arranged by Roger Trefousse) -- 10. Black and White -- 11. Red and Black -- 12. Mural -- 13. Triumph.
      On cassette, "Music from the original score for the PBS film Jackson Pollock: Portrait (1984)."
  - R's, Subseries 18.
    - The Revengers [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1146, Folder 13)
      On container, "Revengers 5008 R1 R2 R3 R4 R5 R6."
    - The Revengers [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1147, Folder 3)
      On container, "Revengers 5008."
    - The Revengers [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1147, Folder 7)
      On container, "Revengers 5008 ??? con't."
    - R.E.L.A.X. -- Post Production Schedule, no. 8, 1986 April 18; 1 pages (Box 1860, Folder 21)
  - S's, Subseries 19.
    - Sketches in Concert -- Scores, orchestral scores (Box 18)
    - Sisters [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1989 April 14; open reel audio tape (Box 1035, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/Sisters/5100-9002/14303/Reel 9/4-14-89."
    - Sisters [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1989 April 14; open reel audio tape (Box 1035, Folder 11)
      On container, "CBS/Sisters/5100-9002/14304/Reel 10/4-14-89."
    - Something Big -- Sound Recordings, 1971 August 4-5; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 3)
      On container, "CCF/8-4 & 8-5-71/R97AADD/DD1-19/#5126 "Something Big"."
    - Something Big --Sound Recordings, 1971 August 4-5; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 4)
      On container, CCF/8-4 & 8-5-71/R97ADD/DD1-19/#5126 "Something Big"."
    - Something Big -- Sound Recordings, 1971 August 4-5; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 5)
      On container, "CCF/8-4 & 8-5-71/R98ADD/DD20-44/#5126 "Something Big"."
    - Senior Citizen Shuffle [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape (Box 1099, Folder 14)
      On container, "Regent Recorded Library/Bridges/Tags/Playoffs/Playons/CTS/"Senior Citizen Shuffle"."
    - Sisters (logs 86-118) -- Sound Recordings, 1989 February 24; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1112, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/2-24-89/R6/LOGS 86-118/"Sisters" (A Lot) Pre-Score."
    - Sisters [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1989 April 14; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1112, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS Music Dept./Sisters 5100-9002/14297/Reel 7 (Safety)/4.14.89."
    - Sisters [Contents Unidentified] -- Sound Recordings, 1989 April 14; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1112, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS Music Dept./Sisters 5100-9002/14300/Reel 10 (Safety)/4.14.89."
    - Something Big -- Sound Recordings, 1971 August 4-5; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 1)
      On container, "CCF/8-4+8-5-71/R98AA/DD20-44/#5126 "Something Big"."
    - Something Big -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 2)
      On container, "CCF/R99A/Piano DD 50-53/#5126 "Something Big"."
    - Something Big -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 3)
      On container, "CCF/R100A/? M12, 32 + 122/#5126 "Something Big"."
    - Stark -- Sound Recordings, 1985 March; Cassette tape (Box 1851)
      Theme by Bill Conti; score by Pete Myers.
    - The Simpsons -- Sound Recordings, 1 sound cassette (Box 1851)
  - T's:, Subseries 20.
    - Thou Shalt Not Kill -- Sound Recordings, 1958 September 4; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1142, Folder 17)
      On container, "KNXT/Main Title End Title."
  - V's, Subseries 22.
    - The Vibrations -- Sound Recordings, 1988 December 8; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1152, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS Ent./The Vibrations/12-8-88/The Watusi, Let's Pony Again."
  - W's, Subseries 23.
    - Who Goes There (logs 5138-5182) -- Sound Recordings, 1965 January 21; open reel audio tape (Box 962, Folder 8)
      On container, "CBS/Who Goes There/Log 5138-5182/1-21-65 R3/5144 8020/MS Mono."
    - Who Goes There (logs 5183-5232) -- Sound Recordings, 1965 January 21; open reel audio tape (Box 962, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/Who Goes There/Log 5183-5232/1-21-65 R4/5144 8020/MS Mono."
    - Who Goes There (logs 5093-5139) -- Sound Recordings, 1965 January 21; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 974, Folder 12)
      On container, "CBS/Who Goes There/Log 5093-5139/1-21-65 R2/5144 8020/3 Trk 01-09."
    - Who Goes There (logs 5138-5182) -- Sound Recordings, 1965 January 21; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 980, Folder 14)
      On container, "CBS/Who Goes There/Log 5138-5182/1-21-65 R3/5144 8020/3 Trk Orig."
    - Who Goes There (logs 5183-5232) -- Sound Recordings, 1965 January 21; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 980, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/Who Goes There/Log 5183-5232/1-21-65 R4/5144 8020/3 Trk Orig."
    - Who Goes There (logs 5058-5092) -- Sound Recordings, 1965 January 21; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 984, Folder 9)
      On container, "CBS/Who Goes There/Log 5058-5092/1-21-65 R1/5144 8020/3 Trk Orig."
    - War End -- Sound Recordings, 1977 December 9; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 18)
      On container, "CTN/12-9-77/R23/Logs415-446/H50-"War End"."
    - War End -- Sound Recordings, 1977 December 9; open reel audio tape (Box 1101, Folder 19)
      On container, "CTN/12-9-77/R24/Logs447-465/H50-"War End""Big Aloha"."
    - Wizard of Elm Street -- Sound Recordings, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1154, Folder 5)
      On container, "Main Title + End Credit Music."
    - Water Under The Bridge -- Sound Recordings., 1987; Cassette tape. (Box 1852)
- Business Papers, Series 7.
  - Assorted Internal Papers, 1981-1990; Subseries 1.; 1 folders
    Undated materials preceed chronologically ordered materials.
    Includes: CBS Hollywood Employee's Club advertisements; organizational charts; blank forms and agreements; film footage tables/time-footage computers; contact lists; studio maps; Education and Training letters; inter-office correspondence; 1988 annual report, and financial reports. Filed in Box 1859, folder 1.
    - AFM reports, 1964-1965 (Box 1789)
    - AFM reports, 1965 [?] (Box 1796)
    - Documents and bios, 1980 [?] (Box 1797)
      Hans Zimmer
    - Memoranda and cue sheets, 1980 [?] (Box 1798)
    - Memoranda, 1980 [?] (Box 1811)
    - Musician's Rolodex (Box 1818)
    - Business records O-Z, 1960-1970 [?] (Box 1824)
      Box 2 of 2
    - Business Records A-N, 1973 (Box 1825)
      Box 1 of 2
    - AFTRA contracts, scores, rehearsal and taping schedules, 1981-1984 (Box 1828)
      On item, "Emmy Awards."
    - Memoranda, scripts and schedules, 1981-1983 (Box 1832)
    - Memoranda and timing sheets, 1964 (Box 1835)
    - Memoranda, 1985 (Box 1836)
    - AFM agreements and documents, 1989 (Box 1838)
  - Financial Records -- General Income and Expenses, Subseries 3.
    - Income and Expenses for August 1987, 1987 September 23; 14 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for August 1987 (nos. 8567-8580)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: CBS Radio Promotion; 6:00 Report; West 57th Street; 5:00 Report; The Morning Program; CND Radio; CND News Special; CBS Sports, and For Our Times.
    - Income and Expenses for April 1987, 1987 May 20; 10 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for April 1987 (nos. 8508-8517).
      Includes billing reports for the following: Sunday Morning; CBS News Special Events; CND Radio News; The Morning Program; CND Special Events, and 6:00 Report.
    - Income and Expenses for August 1989, 1989 September 6; 11 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for August 1989 (nos. 9029-9038)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Radio; Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century); CBS Newsnet; WCBS TV Sports, and CBS Sports.
    - Income and Expenses for August 1990, 1990 November 6; 31 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for August 1990 (nos. 9305-9334)
      Includes billing reports for the following: TV Sports Special; CBS This Morning; CND Radio; Face to Face With Connie Chung; CBS Sports; Radio, Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century); CBS Sports; TV Programs; Newsfeed; 5:00 Report; 60 Minutes, and CND News Special.
    - Income and Expenses for April 1988, 1988 May 27; 21 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for April 1988 (nos. 8717-8737)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: WCBS Radio News 88; CBS Sports; CBS This Morning; 48 Hours; Sunday Morning; Try To Remember; CBS Reports; CND Radio; CBS Radio; Channel 2: The People, and 6:00 Report.
    - Income and Expenses for April 1991, 1991 July 22; 28 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports (nos. 9527-9553)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: Geraldo; CBS This Morning; 1992 Winter Olympics; CBS Sports; Sunday Morning; Boy Meets Girl; Week End News; Joan Rivers Show, and Radio.
    - Income and Expenses for April 1990, 1990 May 30; 19 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for April 1990 (nos. 9209-9226)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Saturday Night With Connie Chung; CND Radio; CBS Sports; CBS This Morning; Paltro Corp.; 60 Minutes; CBS This Morning; Radio, and 11:00 Report.
    - Income and Expenses for August 1988, 1988 September 26; 16 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for August 1988 (nos. 8783-8798)
      Includes billing reports for the following: CND News Promo; CBS Sports; For Our Times; CBS This Morning; We The People; Channel 2: The people, and For Our Times.
    - Income and Expenses for April 1989, 1989 May 22; 27 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for April 1989 (nos. 8933-8958).
      Includes billing reports for the following: West 57th Street; CBS Sports; WCBS TV Programs; CBS This Morning; CBS Radio; Sunday Morning; 5:00 News; CND Radio; WCBS TV Sports; 6:00 Report; CBS Special Events; Radio, Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century), and CND Radio Newsfeed.
    - Income and Expenses for December 1988, 1989 January 24; 30 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for December 1988 (nos. 8846-8874)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Sunday Morning; CBS Sports; CBS This Morning; CBS Radio; 60 Minutes; Radio, Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century); 6:00 Report; West 57th Street, and CND News Promotion.
    - Income and Expenses for December 1990, 1991 January 23; 32 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for December 1990 (nos. 9428-9460)
      Includes billing reports for the following: 5:00 Report; 60 Minutes; CBS This Morning; CBS Sports; CND Radio; Cronkite Tribute; Newsnet, and Radio, Radio (with Walter Cronkite 20th Century).
    - Income and Expenses for December 1987, 1988 January 28; 23 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for December 1987 (nos. 8653-8675)
      Includes billing reports for the following: CND Radio; CND News Promotion; Evening News with Dan Rather; WCBS-TV Editorials; CBS This Morning; CND Radio; The Morning Program; 60 Mintues; 6:00 Report; CND News Promos; NFL Today; Sunday Morning; 48 Hours; CTN Network Advertising & Sales; For Our Times, and CND Radio News.
    - Income and Expenses for February 1988, 1988 March 3; 11 pages; . (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for February 1988 (nos. 8693-8703)
      Includes billing reports for the following: For Our Times; CBS This Morning; Sunday Morning; CBS Sports; 60 Minutes; Morning News, and CND Radio.
    - Income and Expenses for February 1989, 1989 March 3; 29 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for February 1989(nos. 8888-8915).
      Includes billing reports for the following: CBS This Morning; CND News Net; Sunday Morning; CBS Sports; Radio, Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century); WCBS TV Programs; West 57th Street; CBS Radio, and WCBS Radio AM.
    - Income and Expenses for February 1991, 1991 July 1; 18 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for February 1991 (nos. 9476-9492)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: Face to Face With Connie Chung; 60 Minutes; CBS Sports; Geraldo; CBS This Morning; Classic Newsbreak; Radio, Radio (with Walter Cronkite 20th Century), and the Joan Rivers Show.
    - Income and Expenses for February 1987, 1987 March 5; 17 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for February 1987 (nos. 8481-8497)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: Sunday Morning; 6:00 Report; WCBS Radio; West 57th Street; The Morning Program; Morning News; 60 Minutes; Weekend News, and For Our Times.
    - Income and Expenses for July 1987, 1987 August 7; 16 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for July 1987 (nos. 8551-8566)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Sunday Morning; 5:00 Report; CBS Sports; West 57th Street; 6:00 Report; CND Radio; WCBS-TV Special; CBS Evening News with Dan Rather; The Morning Program, and CND News Promotion.
    - Income and Expenses for June 1987, 1987 July 13; 14 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for June 1987 (nos. 8537-8550)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: Sunday Morning; 5:00 Report; The Morning Program; West 57th Street; CND Special Events; 60 Minutes; CBS Radio News; WCBS Radio Promotion; CBS Radio, and CBS Reports.
    - Income and Expenses for January 1987, 1987 February 5; 19 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for January 1987 (nos. 8462-8480)
      Includes billing reports for the following programs: CND Radio News; 6:00 Report; WCBS-TV Promotion; Anerican Treasury; The Morning Program; Late Movie Promo; CBS Sports; CND Network News; Radio Network; Morning News; CBS Radio News; CBS Sports, and Sunday Morning.
    - Income and Expenses for January 1991, 1991 February 13; 16 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for January 1991 (nos. 9461-9475)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Radio, Radio (with Walter Cronkite 20th Century); CBS Radio Promotion; 5:00 Report; CBS Sports; CBS This Morning; Here 2 You, and 60 Minutes.
    - Income and Expenses for July 1990, 1990 August 15; 22 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for July 1990 (nos. 9284-9304)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Project Education; Sunday Morning; Saturday Night With Connie Chung; CBS Radio Sales; Radio, Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century); CBS This Morning; CBS Sports; CND Radio News; Joan Rivers Show, TV Programs.
    - Income and Expenses for June 1990, 1990 August 9; 35 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for June 1990 (nos. 9250-9283)
      Includes billing reports for the following: CBS This Morning; CBS Media Relations; CBS Sports; CBS Religious Special; CND Radio; Sunday Morning; 5:00 News; Joan Rivers Show, and CBS Radio Promotion.
    - Income and Expenses for July 1989, 1989 August 31; 25 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for July 1989(nos. 9004-9028)
      Includes billing reports for the following: WCBS TV Programs; 5:00 Report; Joan Rivers Show; CBS This Morning; Sunday Morning; CND Radio; CBS Sports; CND News Promotion; CND News Special; 6:00 Report; 5:00 Report, and CND Radio.
    - Income and Expenses for June 1989, 1989 July 14; 14 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for June 1989(nos. 8991-9003)
      Includes billing reports for the following: 48 Hours; West 57th; CBS This Morning; CBS Sports Saturday; WCBS TV Sports, and Sunday Morning.
    - Income and Expenses for January 1989, 1989 February 27; 14 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for January 1989 (nos. 8875-8887).
      Includes billing reports for the following: CBS Radio; CND Radio Promotion; 6:00 Report; West 57th Street; CBS This Morning; CBS Sports; 60 Minutes, and Radio, Radio (Walter Cronkite's 20th Century).
    - Income and Expenses for January 1988, 1988 February 18; 17 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for January 1988 (nos. 8676-8692)
      Includes billing reports for the following: 60 Minutes, Sunday Morning; CTN Affiliate Meeting; Cronkite-At-Large; CBS Sports; Weekend News; CBS This Morning; CND Radio; CBS Sports; 6:00 Report; CTN Affiliates, and For Our Times.
    - Income and Expenses for July 1988, 1988 August 25; 10 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for July 1988 (nos. 8773-8782)
      Includes billing reports for the following: CBS Reports; CND Research and Development; CBS Sports; Channel 2: The People; CND Radio; 6:00 Report, and West 57th Street.
    - Income and Expenses for June 1988, 1988 July 25; 11 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for June 1988 (nos. 8762-8772)
      Includes billing reports for the following: West 57th Street; CBS Sports; CND News Promotion; CBS This Morning; Sunday Morning; 6:00 Report; WCBS-TV Programs, and CND Radio.
    - Income and Expenses for May 1988, 1988 June 27; 24 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for May 1988 (nos. 8738-8761)
      Includes billing reports for the following: CBS This Morning; Sunday Morning; West 57th Street; 6:00 Report; For Our Times; CBS Sports; CBS Affiliates Sales; CBS Network Sales; CND Radio; CBS Reports, and News Promotion.
    - Income and Expenses for March 1988, 1988 April 22; 13 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for March 1988 (nos. 8704-8716)
      Includes billing reports for the following: Sunday Morning; For Our Times; 6:00 Report; CBS Sports; CND Radio; Try To Remember; CNS Sports, and 60 Minutes.
    - Income and Expenses for May 1989, 1989 June 22; 33 pages (Box 1757)
      Consists of copies of the Courtesy Billing Reports for May 1989(nos. 8959-8990).